{
  "shortDescription": "Test your trading & market knowledge and get OP token rewards.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is an IPO?",
      "answers": ["Listing", "Merger", "Drop"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is FOMO?",
      "answers": ["Fear", "Greed", "Calm"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is ROI?",
      "answers": ["Return", "Risk", "Growth"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is ATH?",
      "answers": ["High", "Low", "Trade"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Define DEX.",
      "answers": ["Exchange", "Broker", "Bank"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a DApp?",
      "answers": ["App", "Coin", "Token"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Define BNB.",
      "answers": ["Coin", "Stock", "Bond"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is KYC?",
      "answers": ["Know", "Keep", "Kill"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is staking?",
      "answers": ["Earn", "Sell", "Trade"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Define HODL.",
      "answers": ["Hold", "Sell", "Buy"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Define gas.",
      "answers": ["Fee", "Token", "Coin"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a swap?",
      "answers": ["Trade", "Sell", "Mint"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
} 